(Penny:)-Aristotle?
-No.
(Penny:)-Five?
-Oh!
Oh, then I don't know.
(Sheldon:)-Why are you crying?
-Because I'm stupid.
Well, that's no reason to cry.
No, one cries because one is sad.
(Sheldon:)For example, I cry because
others are stupid and it makes me sad.
(Penny:)Look, can we just please forget
about all this extra stuff...
(Penny:)...and can you just tell me
what Leonard does?
(Howard:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Leonard is attempting to learn...
(Sheldon:)...why subatomic particles
move the way they do.
(Penny:)Really? That's it?
Well, that doesn't sound so complicated.
(Sheldon:)It's not. That's why Leonard does it.
(Penny:)Okay, I just have one question.
(Penny:)What exactly are subatomic particles?
(Sheldon:)-A good question.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)And to answer it, we first must
ask ourselves, "What is physics?"